https://lochtay-vacations.co.uk/information/privacy-policy-and-gdpr

Privacy Policy
You are here:HomeInfoPrivacy Policy
We are committed to ensuring the best standards of practice in all our activities. Visitors to our web site and business can be assured that the protection of privacy and confidentiality are given the highest priority. All personal information is collected, held and used in strict compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation 2018.
Please read this privacy notice carefully as it sets out how Largo Leisure and companies within its group use your personal information.
If you have any questions about this privacy notice, please contact us by email: marketing@lochtay-vacations.co.uk
We may change this privacy notice from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure you are happy with any changes.
What does this policy apply to?
This policy covers all information we hold about you, however we obtain it. We collect information at different points during our relationship with you for example, when you browse our website, when you book a holiday, when you are in our parks, if you call our parks, if you sign up to our marketing communications and/or to enter competitions.
What information do we collect and why?
We collect different information depending on what you want to do and how you interact with us. We need to tell you what we use your information for and the legal grounds we have to use it.
Information collected when you use our social media and our websites
Things you do
What information is collected
What is it used for
Our Legal Grounds for collecting information
Browse the website  or using Live Chat (cookies)
Information about your computer, such as which browser you are using, your network location, the type of connection you are using (e.g. broadband, ADSL etc) and your IP address. This is done through cookies. See our Cookie Policy for more detail.
Improving content and functionality on our website.
Legitimate interests to improve our services. The level of information gathered is not intrusive as it is only used to determine if the website works well and to enable Largo Leisure to improve its services.
Enter a competition
If you enter a competition with us we will collect your name, address and contact details.
Administration of the competition and to contact you if you have been successful.
Taking steps at your request prior to entering into a contract.
To ensure we can complete the performance of our contract with you we require you to provide the stated information.
Enter a competition and consent to receive marketing
If you enter a competition and consent to receive marketing, we will collect your name, address and contact details.
Sending direct marketing communications to you.
Legitimate interests of Largo Leisure competitions and other promotions.
Sign up to a newsletter and/or marketing communications
If you request marketing communications we will as a minimum collect your full name and email address.
Sending direct marketing communications to you.
Consent.
You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.  Where consent is the only legal basis for processing, we will cease to process data after consent is withdrawn.
Information collected when you make a booking for a Holiday and/or activities
Things you do
What information is collected
What is it used for
Our Legal Grounds for collecting information
Booking a break
If you book a break, we need the following information as a minimum:
· Name;
· Email address
· Postal address
· Telephone number and type
· Date of birth
· Type/Name of accommodation
· Financial details for payment.
All of the information we request from you is needed in order to book and provide your break.  We cannot provide your break without it.
If an adapted lodge is required the information is used to ensure that we comply with our obligations under equality legislation, by ensuring you have access to our facilities that are suitable for your needs.
Performance of a Contract
To allow us to complete the performance of our contract with you we require you to provide the stated information.
We do not ask for further details of your specific requirements or disability unless you provide us with additional information so that we can make special arrangements during your break (including in relation to medical care).
Information collected while you are on your Holiday
Things you do
What information is collected
What is it used for
Our Legal Grounds for collecting information
Security measures whilst on park
CCTV is in place to monitor and maintain safety of all.
We use CCTV footage to assist in monitoring and maintaining safety within our parks. Where necessary this footage may also be shared with the authorities for law enforcement purposes.
Performance of our contract with you and to comply with health and safety legislation (where applicable).
Visiting Reception
If you visit reception in one of our parks during your holiday to report an issue, fault or complaint the following information is collected, as a minimum:
· Name
· Address
· Lodge details
· Nature of enquiry
This information is used to resolve the enquiry, or progress a complaint as appropriate.
This will be recorded into the relevant recording systems.  The information is also used in case there is a complaint or claim about the holiday.
The legitimate interests of Largo Leisure Holidays to ensure the safety of guests and employees in the parks, and to assist with law enforcement.
This footage may also be used to exercise and defend our legal rights.
Telephoning the Offices
If you contact our office, during or after your break the following information is collected, as a minimum:
· Name
· Address
· Lodge details
· Nature of enquiry
This information is used to resolve the enquiry, or progress a complaint as appropriate.
This will be recorded into the relevant recording systems.  The information is also used in case there is a legal claim about the break.
All data is kept for a period of 7 years and then deleted in accordance with our insurance obligations.
The legitimate interests of Largo Leisure Holidays to ensure the safety of guests and employees in the parks, and to assist with law enforcement.
This footage may also be used to exercise and defend our legal rights.
Medical Assistance
If you require Medical Assistance at one of our parks the following information is collected, as a minimum:
· Name
· Address
· Lodge details
· Nature of enquiry
This will be recorded into our accident book and retained in accordance with our retention policy. It is required by law to register a record of attendance by a medical professional.
The legitimate interests of Largo Leisure Holidays to provide customer services and provide you with an appropriate response to your query.
We may also use this information in order to exercise and defend our legal rights.
On Park incidents
Records of accidents and treatments received.
We are required by law to keep a record of accidents and treatments.
The information is also used in case there is a claim about the cause of the accident and/or the treatments received.
The legitimate interests of Largo Leisure Holidays to provide customer services and provide you with an appropriate response to your query.
We may also use this information in order to exercise and defend our legal rights.
Post Holiday
Things you do
What information is collected
What is it used for
Our Legal Grounds for collecting information
Completing the Trip Advisor Feedback form
If you complete a Trip Advisor review, which is not mandatory, Trip Advisor collects the following information as a minimum.
· Name
· Address
· Lodge details
· Your Feedback
This information is used to provide feedback to the relevant departments in each village and to address an issue or complaint.
Consent
By leaving your feedback with Trip Advisor you give your consent.
You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.  Where consent is the only legal basis for processing, we will cease to process data after consent is withdrawn.
At anytime
Things you do
What information is collected
What is it used for
Our Legal Grounds for collecting information
Contacting our Parks
If you ring our Parks to make an enquiry before booking a break the following information is collected, as a minimum:
· Name
· Address
· Lodge details
· Nature of enquiry
This information is used to resolve the enquiry, or progress a complaint as appropriate.
This will be recorded into the relevant recording systems.  The information is also used in case there is a complaint or claim about the break.
The information will also be used to enable us to learn and continually improve the quality of the service or products we provide.
All data is kept in our system for a period of 7 years and then deleted in accordance with our retention policy.
The legitimate interests of Largo Leisure Holidays to provide customer services and provide you with an appropriate response to your query.
We may also use this information in order to exercise and defend our legal rights.
Where Largo Leisure has legal ground for processing information, you have a right to object to Largo Leisure’s use of this information. If you want to object, contact us at marketing@lochtay-vacations.co.uk
Building profiles and targeting communications
We use profiling and screening techniques to ensure that the communications and offers we send you are personalised, relevant and timely.  We do this because it allows us to understand your background and the background of our guests and enables us to improve your holiday experience.  We also do this so that we can communicate with you in the way that suits you best and to help ensure that you only receive communications and offers that are likely to be of interest to you.
We also use profiling techniques and the information you provide us while you are on one of our sites to better understand what you like doing, for example what restaurants and activities you use. We do this so we can improve our products and services and your experience while you are on holiday with us.
As part of our profiling activities, we will take into account factors such as geographic, demographic and other information relating to you so that we can better understand your interests and preferences. To do this we may use additional information from third party sources when it is available. Such information is compiled using publicly available data about you, for example number of children, age of children, these can be at a variety of levels from postcode area to individual households.
Marketing
So that you are the first to hear about our exciting new offers, activities and facilities, you can opt in to receive this information when you book your Largo Leisure Break. You have the option to opt in to our marketing communications.
If you have given us your consent to receive marketing communications by email, are customers of ours or you have previously asked us for information about our breaks or experiences, we may also send you this information by email. However, in every marketing email message we send you, we will give you the opportunity to unsubscribe from our mailings altogether as well as updating your information.
We use your personal information to tailor the marketing communications we send to you. For example, we track your booking history with us in terms of the accommodation you choose and the activities you and the members of your party do in order to build a picture of the things you like and dislike.  This enables us to provide you with a more personalised service, and give you information about offers and activities, which are more likely to be of interest to you.  We do not provide your personal information to external organisations (i.e. outside of Largo Leisure Holidays) for their own marketing purposes without your explicit consent.
If at any time you do not want your information used for direct marketing purposes or if you decide that you no longer wish to receive marketing emails from us, please either follow the unsubscribe link in one of our marketing email messages or contact us by emailing marketing@lochtay-vacations.co.uk. Please note that if you have a forthcoming booking we will send you service related emails, even if you have unsubscribed from marketing communications, as this is important information you will require for your forthcoming break.
Who do we share this information with?
Our group. Your personal information may be shared with other companies within the Largo Leisure group of companies based in the UK because we operate centralised systems. We may also share your personal information with a purchaser or potential purchaser of our business.
Our suppliers. We may share your personal information with our suppliers, which covers companies from IT services, companies operating activities in our parks, our concession partners (i.e. the shops and restaurants operated by third parties within our parks), property managers, marketing and communications. They only use the information to provide their services to us (such as managing restaurant reservations), in relation to any feedback or complaint you may have about them, or if you have had an accident on the premises of a concession partner, for example.  We only give them the information that they need. We always keep control of your data and our suppliers must act in accordance with our instructions.
Our partners. We will only ever share your personal information with our carefully selected partners and in a manner that does not identify you as an individual or which allows our research partner to identify you as an individual.  We do this with social media partners, such as Facebook and Twitter to participate in their Custom Audience and/or Lookalike Audience programs so that you can receive targeted ads from us when you use the social media site, and so that other users of the site who share similar interests to you can also receive targeted ads from us. We may provide your email address or phone number for this purpose. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, you may opt-out by contacting us at marketing@lochtay-vacations.co.uk.
Legal requirements. In some circumstances, we may have to disclose your personal information by law, because a court or the police or other law enforcement agency has requested it using the appropriate channels.
How long do we keep your information?
We only hold your personal information for as long as is necessary to provide services to you unless there is a requirement to hold that information for a longer period – for example our insurers require us to hold defined information for certain periods of time, or we may have be subject to a statutory obligation to keep hold of your information. If there is a possibility that you may have a legal claim against us, for example if you have had an accident in one of our parks, or have made a complaint about a break with us, then we will hold your information for the duration of any statutory limitation period associated with such legal claims.
Children
Our website is not targeted at children but in any event personal information will not knowingly be collected from children under sixteen years without parental consent. We do not accept bookings from any persons under the age of Eighteen years of age.
Data Security
We take appropriate measures to safeguard the information we hold from unauthorised access or improper use. Our database is stored in a secure, password protected location. Only users authorised by us have access to this data.
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect, including locked cabinets, data encryption and electronic password protection.
If at any point you suspect or become aware of a security incident (i.e. You receive suspicious communication from someone holding themselves out to be a Largo Leisure employee or from a dupe website claiming to be affiliated with Largo Leisure), please forward the communication to us or report the incident by email to marketing@lochtay-vacations.co.uk If you have been the victim of a fraudulent transaction please always contact the police and/or your bank in the first instance to ensure your own finances are secure.
How to get copies of your information
To request details of the personal information that we hold about you pleaseemail us at marketing@lochtay-vacations.co.uk
Amending your information
If your details change, or if you think any information we have about you is wrong or incomplete, please correct it by emailing us on marketing@lochtay-vacations.co.uk. We will correct or update any information as soon as we can.
Complaints to the regulator
If you do not think that we have processed your data in accordance with this notice, please contact us by email at marketing@lochtay-vactions.co.uk.
If you are not satisfied with our response, you can refer the matter to the Information Commissioner's Office. Information about how to do this is available on his website at www.ico.org.uk.
Largo Leisure Group
The companies in the Largo Leisure group covered by this privacy notice are:
· Loch Tay Highland Lodges - Company number: SC293700 Address: Loch Tay Highland Lodges, Killin, FK21 8TY
· Braidhaugh Holiday Park -  Company number: SC298909, Address: Briadhaugh Holiday Park, Crieff PH7 4DH
· Sauchope Holiday Park  Company number: SC244671, Address: Sauchope Links Holiday Park, Crail, Anstruther KY10 3XJ
· Letham Feus Holiday Park  Company number: SC262177, Address: Letham Feus Holiday Park, Cupar Rd, Leven KY8 5NT
